<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Chandigarh Guide App</string>

    <string name="jwdesc">JW Marriott Hotels and Resorts is a luxury hotel chain that is a brand of Marriott International.It is marvelous piece of architecture and a 5 star rating hotel.The Hotel is in sector 35,Chandigarh. </string>
    <string name="Tajhotel">aj Chandigarh, one of the best 5-star hotels in Chandigarh, celebrates the dynamic spirit of the city in its sophisticated architecture and interiors. Built only recently, the hotel is located in Sector 17, the city’s prime business and shopping area. Our guests can make the most of its convenient location, as the hotel is a comfortable 30-minute drive from the airport and a 15-minute drive from the railway station.</string>
    <string name="Lalit">The LaLiT Chandigarh, draws inspirations from Le Corbusier in its interiors and architecture. Overlooking the Shivalik range, the hotel is located in Rajiv Gandhi IT Park – city’s business hub, just minutes away from the railway station.The hotel offers 179 spacious and well-appointed rooms and suites offering breathtaking view of the Shivallik hills, six distinctive dining outlets, the super-luxe nightclub Kitty Su, the award-winning Rejuve – The Spa, the largest convention centre and luxurious banqueting space.</string>

    <string name="ivyhospital">Ivy Hospital Mohali, is the First Flagship Hospital of Ivy Healthcare Group. It is a 205 bed multi Super Speciality Tertiary Care Hospital.The hospital started its operations way back in 2008 and now after 7 years in Operation, it is among the leading hospital in the region. It is the first hospital in Ivy Group of hospitals to get NABH Accreditation.It is a state-of-the art modern facility situated in a prominent location at Mohali. It has a built-up area of over 1,50,000 square feet. Right from the infrastructure to the latest medical technology acquisition.</string>
    <string name="PGI">The Postgraduate Institute of Medical Education and Research (or PGIMER) is a medical and research institution located in Chandigarh, India. It has educational, medical research and training facilities for its students.PGIMER is involved in research for the rural and community related environment and health problems. The focus of research has been on tackling diseases like diarrhoea, tuberculosis, malaria, amoebiasis Systemic vasculitis, Relapsing polychondritis, HIV, leprosy, hepatitis, anaemia, leukaemia, hypertension, atherosclerosis, thalassemia, dental caries, stone disease, cancer, and sexually transmitted diseases.</string>
    <string name="Fortis">Fortis Healthcare Limited is a leading integrated healthcare delivery service provider in India. The healthcare verticals of the company primarily comprise hospitals, diagnostics and day care specialty facilities.Approximately 10,000 potential beds and 314 diagnostic centres.In a global study of the 30 most technologically advanced hospitals in the world, its flagship, the Fortis  was ranked No.2</string>

    <string name="Elante">Elante Mall is a shopping mall in the city of Chandigarh in India. With the gross leasable area of 1,150,000 sq ft, it is the second largest shopping mall in Northern India and the third largest in India. Elante is spread over 20 acres of area.Elante Mall has a retail space of over 1 million square feet. In the retail area, Elante Mall hosts retailers of various Indian and international brands a food court and a courtyard full of cafes. The Mall has an 8-screen Multiplex of PVR Cinemas. On its top floor, the mall has restaurants and fast food joints. For kids entertainment there is a Fun City on the top floor.</string>
    <string name="NCM">The North Country Mall is developed by Gumberg India, one of the largest privately held real estate development firms in the country. This has been designed by renowned U.S.-based architects, TVS Design.The Mall features three grand drop-off points, superior Ingress and Egress, and copious surface and basement parking which will give the visitors a hassle-free shopping experience. The design also incorporates an amphi theatre at the North Entrance and a grand South Piazza as two large distinctive public spaces for community-centered events.</string>

    <string name="sukhnalake">Sukhna Lake in Chandigarh, India, is a reservoir at the foothills (Shivalik hills) of the Himalayas. This 3 km² rainfed lake was created in 1958 by damming the Sukhna Choe, a seasonal stream coming down from the Shivalik Hills.Sukhna Lake is the venue for many festive celebrations, too. The most popular is the Mango Festival held during the monsoons when scores of varieties of mangoes are on display. From time-to-time, other food festivals featuring specialties from different Indian States are also held here, along with cultural performances.</string>
    <string name="rosegarden">Zakir Hussain Rose Garden, is a botanical garden located in Chandigarh, India and spread over 30 acres (120,000 m2) of land, with 50,000 rose-bushes of 1600 different species.Apart from serving as a host of other events, the Zakir Rose Garden serves as the venue for hosting an annual rose festival called Rose Festival, a major cultural event in Chandigarh during February or March. Celebrated mainly as a tribute to the magnificence of the rose itself, the attractions include food, drinks, joyrides, and contests of varying nature, such as photography, gardening, landscaping, bonsai, and Rose Prince and Princess. The contests are open to the residents or institutions from nearby places.</string>
    <string name="rockgarden">The Rock Garden of Chandigarh is a sculpture garden in Chandigarh, India, also known as Nek Chand Rock Garden after its founder Nek Chand, a government official who started the garden secretly in his spare time in 1957. Today it is spread over an area of 40 acres (161874.25 m2). It is completely built of industrial and home waste and thrown-away itemsIn his spare time, Nek Chand started collecting materials from demolition sites around the city. He recycled these materials into his own vision of the divine kingdom of Sukrani, choosing a gorge in a forest near Sukhna Lake for his work.It had grown into a 12-acre (49,000 m2) complex of interlinked courtyards, each filled with hundreds of pottery-covered concrete sculptures of dancers, musicians, and animals</string>

    <string name="hotel1">JW MARIOTT</string>
    <string name="hotel2">Taj Hotel</string>
    <string name="hotel3">Lalit Hotel</string>

    <string name="hospital1">Ivy Hospital</string>
    <string name="hospital2">PGI</string>
    <string name="hospital3">Fortis Hospital</string>

    <string name="mall1">Elante Mall</string>
    <string name="mall2">North Country Mall</string>

    <string name="place1">Sukhna Lake</string>
    <string name="place2">Rose Garden</string>
    <string name="place3">Rock Garden</string>

</resources>
